1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 60.
This is how many books an average CEO reads a year.
Here are some hacks that would help you reach that number.
The moment there is a book that you're not feeling,
just throw it away, don't worry about it,
and take a book that you really, really like.
That way you will make it a habit.
Set yourself embarrassingly tiny goals.
For example, instead of wanting to read a book a week,
which is quite a big goal,
set yourself a goal to read half a page before sleep.
That way you can't check it out.
When you're chilling or waiting for something,
you naturally get distracted.
And then the thing that you do is you grab a phone.
So set a screen saver that says,
read more or read a book instead.
That way instead of scoring social media, you'll be reading.
Your brain gets bored really quickly.
In order to make it exciting for yourself,
read in a few different languages.
Studies also show that it literally speeds up
your cognitive ability.
Force yourself to read in situations and settings
when it's least convenient.
For example, in the shower.
That way, when you're chilled,
reading on a sofa and extra fireplace,
will be a piece of cake.