Have you ever wondered who is behind the financing of Saudi Arabia's crazy mega projects? It is the richest family in the world, and  you've never even heard of them.
They have gold toilets, gold Lamborghinis, and even purchased the world's most expensive house,
a 300 million castle in France.
However, this is just a small part of their overall wealth.
The family is the house of Saud, and they own Saudi Aramco, the largest company in the entire world,
which is responsible for all of Saudi Arabia's oil reserves,
and they definitely know how to spend their money.
Their combined assets, including a net worth of over $1.4 trillion,
make them richer than the British royal family.
Despite their lavish lifestyle, the house of Saud also demonstrates a profound ambition to shape the future of Saudi Arabia,
directing their immense resources towards the nation's transformative mega projects.